Clement F. Haynsworth Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- United States Court of Appeals File, 1955-1989 (Box 6-201)
  - Case File, 1956-1989 (Box 7-159)
    - 1972 October term
      - United States v. Slosberg, No. 73-1185
      - Smith v. Koerber, No. 73-1186
      - United States v. Calley, No. 73-1197
      - Horton v. Royal Indem. Co., No. 73-1216
      - Crosson v. Vance, No. 73-1222
      - United States v. Walke, No. 73-1316
      - William F. Wilke, Inc. v. Department of the Army, No. 73-1483 (Box 27)
      - United States v. Sheppard, No. 73-1504
      - United States v. McIe, No. 73-1539
      - United States v. Sheppard, No. 73-1547
      - United States v. Sheppard, No. 73-1548
      - Cape Henry Bird Club v. Laird, No. 73-1606
      - Marine Atl. Corp. v. Dent, No. 73-8016
    - 1973 October term
      - Brewer v. School Bd. of Norfolk, No. 71-1900
      - Gold v. Sloan, No. 71-2180
      - United States v. Gibson, No. 72-1697
      - United States v. Ghiz, No. 72-1728
      - United States v. Turner, No. 72-2035
      - United States v. Amdusky, No. 72-2457
      - United States v. Davis, No. 72-2486
      - United States v. Boone, No. 73-1080
      - Chapa v. American Bank, No. 73-1155
      - A. J. Legum Stores Corp. v. Creditor's Comm., No. 73-1198
      - United States v. Padnick, No. 73-1252
      - United States v. Barr, No. 73-1269
      - Dickerson v. Weinberger, No. 73-1275
      - B. A. Berkus Assocs. v. Keen, No. 73-1288
      - United States v. Stanley, No. 73-1312
      - In re Certain land situate, Worcester, Md., No. 73-1323
      - United States v. Snellings, No. 73-1380
      - United States v. Moulden, No. 73-1399 (Box 28)
      - Schultz v. United States, No. 73-1406
      - United States v. Brooks, No. 73-1441
      - Misegades, Douglas & Levy v. Strauch, Nolan, Neale, Nies & Kurz, No. 73-1464
      - United States v. Scott, No. 73-1514
      - Dunheen v. Bounds, No. 73-1521
      - Devlin Lumber & Supply Corp. v. United States, No. 73-1530
      - United Transp. Union v. Patapsco & Back River R.R., No. 73-1575
      - United States v. Dillis, No. 73-1582
      - Robertson v. Railroad Retirement Bd., No. 73-1593
      - United States v. Williams, No. 73-1594
      - Maddox v. Board of Trustees, Anderson Pub. Schools, No. 73-1602
      - United States v. Wright, No. 73-1608
      - Janetta v. Cole, No. 73-1642
      - United States v. Tinsley, No. 73-1653
      - United States v. Taylor, No. 73-1667
      - United States v. Williams, No. 73-1694
      - United States v. Wynn, No. 73-1749
      - Baker v. Huntley, No. 73-1771
      - United States v. Porter, No. 73-1773
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 73-1779
      - United States v. Davis, No. 73-1797
      - United States v. Schulz, No. 73-1800
      - United States v. Bauer, No. 73-1835
      - Williams v. Hyde County Bd. of Educ., No. 73-1863
      - United States v. Brewer, No. 73-1901
      - United States v. Curry, No. 73-1931
      - Aron v. Laird, No. 73-1941
      - United States v. Moore, No. 73-1946
      - United States v. Sharpe, No. 73-1954
      - Pollard v. Osteen, No. 73-1961
      - United States v. Wright, No. 73-1963
      - Eaddy v. Compania Sud-Americana de Vapores, No. 73-1966
      - United States v. Gerald, No. 73-2013
      - United States v. Dixon, No. 73-2020
      - United States v. Brown, No. 73-2046
      - Swann v. Charlotte-Mecklenburg Bd. of Educ., No. 73-2048 (Box 29)
      - Chandler v. Secretary of Health, Educ. and Welfare, No. 73-2059
      - Kline v. Employers' Commercial Union Ins. Co., No. 73-2060
      - United States v. McGrane, No. 73-2074
      - United States v. Mankins, No. 73-2120
      - United States v. Taylor, No. 73-2153
      - United States v. Cremeans, No. 73-2166
      - Green v. School Bd. of Roanoke, No. 73-2181
      - United States v. Coston, No. 73-2192
      - United States v. Dove, No. 73-2193
      - Doe v. Boyle, No. 73-2218
      - Warren v. DeBell, No. 73-2221
      - Securities and Exch. Comm'n v. Haffenden-Rimar Int'l, No. 73-2297
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n v. Cleveland Mills Co., No. 73-2298
      - United States v. Thompson, No. 73-2341
      - Wilmington Shipping Co. v. International Longshoremen's Ass'n, No. 73-2354
      - United States v. Gibson, No. 73-2467
      - Wilson v. Newport News Lodge No. 315, No. 73-2468
      - United States v. Clark, No. 73-2478
      - Craven v. Hartford Fire Ins. Co., No. 73-2501
      - United States v. Morrow, No. 74-1049
      - United States v. Jones, No. 74-1074
      - United States v. Stollings, No. 74-1087
      - United States v. Vann, No. 74-1091
      - White v. Chesapeake & Ohio Ry. Co., No. 74-1096
      - United States v. Bethea, No. 74-1099
      - United States v. Nantahala Power & Light Co., No. 74-1122
      - Shaw Real Estate v. Melnick, No. 74-1146
      - United States v. Jordan, No. 74-1258
      - United States v. Rocks, No. 74-1262
      - Harrington v. Holshouser, No. 74-1320
      - United States v. Williams, No. 74-1501
      - United States v. Gorham, No. 74-1540
      - White Bag Co. v. International Paper Co., No. 74-1552
    - 1974 October term (Box 30)
      - Walker v. Dillard, No. 73-1108
      - United Appalachian Poor People v. Webster County Memorial Hosp., No. 73-1663
      - Metzger v. Hertz Corp., No. 73-1720
      - Stepheney v. United States, No. 73-1829
      - United States v. Alston, No. 73-2162
      - Hicks v. Leeke, No. 73-2281
      - McCrary v. Runyon, No. 73-2348; (4 folders)
      - Conway v. Hawkins, No. 73-2357
      - United States v. Fabian, No. 74-1032
      - Urban Sys. Dev. Corp. v. NCNB Mortgage Corp., No. 74-1101 (Box 31)
      - Clark v. Maryland, No. 74-1126
      - Rhone-Poulenc S.A. v. Dann, No. 74-1136
      - Paynter v. Chesapeake and Ohio Ry., No. 74-1210
      - Becker v. Paul, No. 74-1219
      - Jones Wholesale Co. v. General Accident Fire and Life Assurance Corp., No. 74-1244
      - MacKeithan v. Virginia, No. 74-1249
      - Tanglewood Mall v. Chase Manhattan Bank, No. 74-1250
      - Moore v. United States, No. 74-1260
      - Fidelity Bankers Life Ins. Co. v. Williams, No. 74-1269
      - Shepherd v. Gathright, No. 74-1273
      - Roberts v. A. B. Dick Co., No. 74-1318
      - Smith v. McDonald's Corp., No. 74-1321
      - United States v. Terry, No. 74-1325
      - United States v. Slaughter, No. 74-1341
      - United States v. Smith, No. 74-1361
      - United States v. Pollard, No. 74-1368
      - Pierce v. Schlesinger, No. 74-1375
      - Sperry Rand Corp. v. A-T-O, No. 74-1413
      - United States v. Jefferson, No. 74-1469
      - United States v. Crouse, No. 74-1470
      - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc. v. Colby, No. 74-1478; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Warren, No. 74-1492 (Box 32)
      - McGhee v. Lucas, No. 74-1524
      - Colter Corp. v. Commissioner, No. 74-1527
      - United States v. Quicksey, No. 74-1559
      - Trenton Livestock v. Butz, No. 74-1644
      - United States v. Sellers, No. 74-1654
      - United States v. Anderson, No. 74-1694
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Santee River Wool Combing Co., No. 74-1746
      - United States v. Sawyers, No. 74-1769
      - United States v. Lynch, No. 74-1774
      - United States v. Brooks, No. 74-1783
      - United States v. Ellisor, No. 74-1809
      - McGuffin v. Weinberger, No. 74-1833
      - Trammel v. Kelly, No. 74-1962
      - United States v. Miller, No. 74-1967
      - Kimes v. United States, No. 74-1982
      - United States v. Wyatt, No. 74-2017
      - Demby v. Weinberger, No. 74-2019
      - Rosenberg v. Commissioner, No. 74-2037
      - Schrader v. Dyer, No. 74-2046
      - United States v. Holley, No. 74-2049
      - Spencer v. CIE Maritime Belge, No. 74-2055
      - United States v. Williams, No. 74-2065
      - United States v. Mizani, No. 74-2072
      - Shea v. United States, No. 74-2115
      - United States v. Davis, No. 74-2139
      - United States v. Huffman, No. 74-2185
      - United States v. Thompson, No. 74-2213
      - United States v. Hamlin, No. 74-2231
      - McCray v. Boslow, No. 74-2252
      - Gibson v. South Carolina, No. 74-2256
      - United States v. Jones, No. 74-2307
      - United States v. Goodrich, No. 74-2399
      - United States v. Marsh, No. 75-1032 (Box 33)
      - United States v. Candie, No. 75-1040
      - Revels v. Weinberger, No. 75-1046
      - United States v. Proffitt, No. 75-1123
      - United States v. Flebotte, No. 75-1131
      - Stacy v. Virginia Elec. and Power Co., No. 75-1166
      - Taylor v. Ivey, No. 75-1185
      - United States v. Boswell, No. 75-1216
      - Parker v. W. W. Moore & Sons, No. 75-1232
      - United States v. Stollings, No. 75-1244
      - United States v. Harris, No. 75-1317
    - 1975 October term
      - Baugh v. United States, No. 73-2304
      - Lovisi v. Slayton, No. 73-2337
      - Star v. Benton, No. 73-2390
      - Stebbins v. Nationwide Mut. Ins. Co., No. 74-1051
      - Spratley v. Paderick, No. 74-1326
      - Russell v. Interstate Towing Co., No. 74-1519
      - Thomas v. Ward, No. 74-1541
      - Harrington v. Schlesinger, No. 74-1573 (Box 34)
      - United States v. Baechler, No. 74-1595
      - South Carolina State Highway Dep't v. Brinegar, No. 74-1613
      - United States v. Hawkins, No. 74-1636
      - Harrison v. United Transp. Union, No. 74-1737
      - Pryor v. Calmar S.S. Corp., No. 74-1825
      - Scharf v. Commissioner, No. 74-1827
      - Professional Eng'rs v. United States, No. 74-1848
      - United States v. Poindexter, No. 74-1920
      - Resendez v. Garrison, No. 74-1930
      - United States v. Futeral, No. 74-1934
      - Oriente Commercial v. American Flag Vessel, No. 74-1966
      - Richards v. Blake Builders Supply, No. 74-2010
      - United States v. White, No. 74-2024
      - Committee for Consideration of the Jones Falls Sewage Sys. v. Train, No. 74-2076 (Box 35)
      - United States v. Powell, No. 74-2079
      - United States v. Leonard, No. 74-2127
      - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac R.R. v. Commissioner, No. 74-2146
      - Union Boiler Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 74-2150
      - International Tel. & Tel. v. General Tel. & Elec., No. 74-2158
      - Lane v. United States, No. 74-2169
      - United States v. Battle, No. 74-2170
      - Jordan v. Simonds Abrasive Div., No. 74-2184
      - Lewron Television v. D. H. Overmyer Leasing Co., No. 74-2227
      - United States v. Rodney, No. 74-2271
      - United States v. Baranov, No. 74-2284
      - Doggett v. Ritter Fin. Co., No. 74-2287
      - Reamer v. United States, No. 74-2290
      - United States v. 112.72 acres of land, Grayson County, Va., No. 74-2325
      - Kidd v. Pollard, No. 74-2374
      - Ricard v. Birch, No. 74-2377
      - United States v. Walters, No. 75-1048
      - Tabory v. United States, No. 75-1081
      - Shaffer v. United States, No. 75-1092 (Box 36)
      - United States v. Snead, No. 75-1156
      - United States v. Prescimone, No. 75-1170
      - United States v. Smith, No. 75-1179
      - United States v. Atkinson, No. 75-1207
      - United States v. Chatman, No. 75-1221
      - Sauerhoff v. Hearst Corp., No. 75-1229
      - United States v. Adams, No. 75-1247
      - United States v. Preston, No. 75-1249
      - United States v. Allen, No. 75-1299
      - Dunlop v. Ashworth, No. 75-1311
      - Ruiz v. Prudential Ins. Co., No. 75-1339
      - Harris v. Ulanich, No. 75-1358
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n v. International Longshoremen's Ass'n, No. 75-1376
      - Carini v. United States, No. 75-1399; (2 folders)
      - Estate of Thalheimer v. Commissioner, No. 75-1413 (Box 37)
      - Thurston v. Ford Motor Co., No. 75-1434
      - United States v. Mathis, No. 75-1436
      - Whalen v. Marini, No. 75-1438
      - United States v. Branch, No. 75-1439
      - Williams v. Board of Educ. of Kanawha, No. 75-1455
      - Hatfield v. Mullins Ford, No. 75-1484
      - Azalea Drive-In-Theatre v. Hanft, No. 75-1504
      - McLamore v. Weinberger, No. 75-1511
      - United States v. Chatman, No. 75-1532
      - Sobus v. Lumberman's Mut. Casualty Co., No. 75-1555
      - Robinson v. Weinberger, No. 75-1579
      - United States v. Mules, No. 75-1585
      - Lin v. United States Immigration and Naturalization Serv., No. 75-1587
      - Royal v. Maryland, No. 75-1589
      - United States v. Blackburn, No. 75-1597
      - Boeckenhaupt v. United States, No. 75-1638
      - Burke v. Levi, No. 75-1695
      - United States v. Robinson, No. 75-1697
      - United States v. Jones, No. 75-1705
      - United States v. Lindsey, No. 75-1717
      - United States v. Smith, No. 75-1722
      - Brown v. Mandel, No. 75-1735 (Box 38)
      - Great United Realty Co. v. United States, No. 75-1736
      - Atlantic & Gulf Stevedores v. Tug Dalmatian, No. 75-1761
      - R. C. Stanhope, Inc. v. Roanoke Constr. Co., No. 75-1804
      - Hamby v. United States, No. 75-1828
      - United States v. Ordonez, No. 75-1831
      - Smith v. Weinberger, No. 75-1835
      - Sharpe v. Jones, No. 75-1872
      - Fraley v. Mathews, No. 75-1873
      - Vecco Concrete Constr. v. Ranger Constr. Co., No. 75-1893
      - Luther v. International Ass'n of Bridge Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Local 16, No. 75-1899
      - Sharp v. Berkey, No. 75-1903
      - Molony v. Gilbert, No. 75-1909
      - White v. Mathews, No. 75-1917
      - United States v. Limer, No. 75-1955
      - United States v. Terry, No. 75-1957
      - United States v. Pinckney, No. 75-1975
      - United States v. Wright, No. 75-2002
      - Statewide Realty Corp. v. Atlantic Dep't Stores, No. 75-2027
      - Healy v. Tug Falcon, No. 75-2033
      - United States v. Cunningham, No. 75-2046
      - Hatton v. City of Henderson, No. 75-2061
      - Smith v. United States, No. 75-2072
      - Brown v. Brannon, No. 75-2111 (Box 39)
      - Campbell v. Superintendent, Va. State Penitentiary, No. 75-2116
      - United States v. Wilson, No. 75-2120
      - Turner v. Commissioner, No. 75-2137
      - United States v. Carroll, No. 75-2144
      - United States v. Hall, No. 75-2147
      - Swiss Credit Bank v. Virginia Nat'l Bank, No. 75-2154
      - United States v. Branch, No. 75-2156
      - Small v. Gibson, No. 75-2170
      - Lackey v. United States, No. 75-2192
      - Fikes v. Lewis, No. 75-2201
      - Golden v. Lascara, No. 75-2217
      - Keplinger v. Superintendent, Md. Correctional Inst., No. 75-2253
      - United States v. Hummer, No. 75-2254
      - Perry v. Warden, Md. Penitentiary, No. 75-2297
      - Tatham v. Mathews, No. 75-2303
      - United States v. Allen, No. 75-2316
      - United States v. Pruitt, No. 75-2318
      - United States v. Johnson, No. 75-2320
      - United States v. Harrison, No. 75-2341
      - Chaulk v. Peninsula Shipbuilders Ass'n, No. 76-1007
      - United States v. Herron, No. 76-1062
      - United States v. Jones, No. 76-1069
      - Aldred v. Duling, No. 76-1076
    - 1976 October term
      - United States v. Newsome, No. 75-1053
      - Davis v. Marshall, No. 75-1109
      - United States v. Hayes, No. 75-1239 (Box 40)
      - Higginbotham v. United States, No. 75-1487
      - United States v. Horger, No. 75-1645
      - United States v. Sims, No. 75-1714
      - Powers v. Sims and Levin, No. 75-1768
      - Blackmon v. Blackledge, No. 75-1827
      - Edens v. Commissioner, No. 75-1885
      - United States v. Allen, No. 75-1965
      - United States v. Floyd, No. 75-2044
      - United States v. Bowden, No. 75-2078
      - United States v. McFadden, No. 75-2092
      - Vaughan v. Southern Ry., No. 75-2107
      - Lamb v. Lang, No. 75-2240
      - Midgett v. McClelland, No. 75-2338
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Pine Valley Div., No. 75-2339 (Box 41)
      - Woodard v. Watkins, No. 75-8247
      - United States v. Konstantinot, No. 76-1010
      - United States v. Daniels, No. 76-1018
      - United States v. Chapman, No. 76-1048
      - United States v. Goff, No. 76-1049
      - Roberts v. Collins, No. 76-1080
      - United States v. Fernell, No. 76-1083
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Pilot Freight Carriers, No. 76-1089
      - United States v. Ginyard, No. 76-1146
      - Sine v. Mitchell Trans., No. 76-1201
      - Acero Panama, S.A. v. Vercon Prods., No. 76-1210
      - Lowther v. Montgomery County, No. 76-1229
      - Ideal Realty Co. v. United States, No. 76-1242 (Box 42)
      - United States v. Hudson, No. 76-1276
      - Kornahrens v. Bourne, No. 76-1306
      - Degler v. Lake Holiday Estates, No. 76-1309
      - United States v. Gilbert, No. 76-1311
      - Mahanes v. Hall, No. 76-1321
      - United States v. Dumeur, No. 76-1358
      - Washington Metro. Area Transit Auth. v. One parcel of land, Montgomery County, Md., No. 76-1380
      - United States v. Watkins, No. 76-1402
      - Bauer v. Gilliam, No. 76-1418
      - Board of Supervisors v. Western Engine Co., No. 76-1427
      - Kendall v. Bethlehem Steel Corp., No. 76-1454
      - United States v. Parrish, No. 76-1456
      - G. C. Murphy Co. v. National Labor Relations Bd., No. 76-1470
      - Faircloth v. State Farm Mut. Auto. Ins. Co., No. 76-1484
      - Webb v. Mathews, No. 76-1516
      - National Labor Relations Bd. v. Shen-Mar Food Prods., No. 76-1519
      - Campbell v. Superintendent, Bland Correctional Field Unit, No. 76-1533
      - United States v. Tomaselli, No. 76-1544
      - Peroff v. Hylton, No. 76-1562 (Box 43)
      - Eddin v. Benedict College, No. 76-1570
      - Hinson v. Mathews, No. 76-1613
      - United States v. Hocker, No. 76-1625
      - Hillary v. I.T.O. Corp., No. 76-1627
      - Pou v. Martin, No. 76-1674
      - Brady v. Alderman, No. 76-1680
      - Fender v. Riddle, No. 76-1750
      - Brooks v. United States, No. 76-1790
      - Fleetwood v. Maryland, No. 76-1796
      - Gould v. Gavett, No. 76-1801
      - Edens v. Mathews, No. 76-1834
      - Morris v. Mathews, No. 76-1835
      - Seaboard Coast Line R.R. v. Pilot Freight Carriers, No. 76-1864
      - In re Thomas A. Cary, Inc., No. 76-1879
      - Krasnow v. Virginia Polytechnic Inst., No. 76-1899
      - Calhoun v. United States, No. 76-1902
      - Mullins v. Seals, No. 76-1959
      - United States v. Mattes, No. 76-1963
      - United States v. Walker, No. 76-1965
      - Hawkins v. Mathews, No. 76-1975 (Box 44)
      - United States v. Wilson, No. 76-2021
      - United States v. DeRose, No. 76-2040
      - United States v. Jones, No. 76-2056
      - United States v. Spriggs, No. 76-2069
      - Equal Employment Opportunity Comm'n v. Wood, Wire, and Metal Lathers Union, Local 11, No. 76-2135
      - Whitfield v. Federal Crop Ins. Corp., No. 76-2274
      - United States v. Moore, No. 76-2276
      - United States v. Offit, No. 76-2277
      - Reeves v. General Foods Corp., No. 76-2299
      - United States v. Phillips, No. 76-2316
      - United States v. Jackson, No. 76-2359
      - Merker v. Merker, No. 76-2441
      - Universal Leaf Tobacco Co. v. Congoleum Corp., No. 77-1159
      - Slaughter v. United States, No. 77-1164
      - Overmyer v. Lawyers Title Ins. Corp., No. 77-1343
      - Welsh v. Ponder, No. 77-1466
      - Peroff v. Hylton, No. 77-1729
    - 1977 October term
      - Capital Investors Co. v. Executors of the estate of Morrison, No. 75-1498; (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 45)
      - Hirst v. Commissioner, No. 75-1543
      - Rimmer v. Fayetteville Police Dep't, No. 75-1913
      - Matthews v. United States, No. 75-2171
      - Townsend v. Gratz, No. 75-2332
      - Fowler v. First Am. Land Corp., No. 76-1082
      - United States v. Hemrich, No. 76-1092
      - United States v. Jemal, No. 76-1170
      - United States v. Revels, No. 76-1343
      - American Lease Plans v. Boineau, No. 76-1396
      - United States v. Roberts, No. 76-1462 (Box 46)
      - Edmonds v. Compagnie Generale Transatlantique, No. 76-1545; (3 folders)
      - United States v. Holt, No. 76-1602
      - Ball v. Mathews, No. 76-1727
      - United States v. Agunbiade, No. 76-1776
      - Somerville v. Mathews, No. 76-1833
      - United States v. West, No. 76-1837; (3 folders)
      - United States v. Turnbull, No. 76-1857
      - Cramer v. Virginia Commonwealth Univ., No. 76-1937; (1 folder) (Box 47)
      - Washington Metro. Area Transit Auth. v. Two parcels of land, Fairfax County, Va., No. 76-1960
      - Cullum Elec. & Mechanical v. Mechanical Contractors Ass'n, No. 76-2074; (2 folders)
      - United States v. Gorin, No. 76-2136
      - United States v. Waldrop, No. 76-2210
      - United States v. Thurston Motor Lines, No. 76-2230; (2 folders)
      - Masters v. Baker, No. 76-2292
      - United States v. Calabrese, No. 76-2405
      - Robinson v. North Am. Van Lines, No. 76-2412
      - Hartford Casualty Ins. Co. v. Dodd, No. 76-2448
      - Black, Inc. v. United States Fidelity & Guar. Co., No. 76-2453
      - Johnson v. Commissioner, No. 77-1010 (Box 48)
      - Niles v. United States Navy, No. 77-1033
      - Irby v. Metropolitan Life Ins. Co., No. 77-1035
      - In re Nepratex Indus., No. 77-1059
      - Nottingham v. Zahradnick, No. 77-1095
      - United States v. Squire, No. 77-1135
      - United States v. Hocker, No. 77-1156
      - United States v. Marable, No. 77-1173
      - Williams v. Zahradnick, No. 77-1181
      - Gardner v. Paderick, No. 77-1185
      - Jackson v. Virginia, No. 77-1205
      - United States v. Bass, No. 77-1208
      - United States v. Garner, No. 77-1222
      - Boeing Co. v. Radiation Sys., No. 77-1230
      - Carter v. Boston Old Colony Ins. Co., No. 77-1256
      - Excavation Constr. v. Difco, No. 77-1272
      - DiPaola v. Riddle, No. 77-1293
      - United States v. Parker, No. 77-1323
      - United States v. Rogers, No. 77-1365 (Box 49)
      - In re Bazen, No. 77-1374
      - Fabritz v. Traurig, No. 77-1411; (2 folders)
      - Gibson v. Zahradnick, No. 77-1415
      - United States v. Scott, No. 77-1429
      - Rice v. McKenzie, No. 77-1475
      - Powell v. Currey, No. 77-1486
      - Interstate Towing Co. v. City Ice and Fuel Co., No. 77-1488
      - United States v. Taylor, No. 77-1498
      - Tibbs v. Minor, No. 77-1509
      - O'Connor v. Jarvis, No. 77-1559
      - United States v. Moore, No. 77-1568
      - Hood v. Califano, No. 77-1572
      - Turner v. Western Life Ins. Co., No. 77-1581
      - Anderson v. Southern Discount Co., No. 77-1587
      - Patsey v. Califano, No. 77-1605
      - Weston v. Security Nat'l Bank, No. 77-1607
      - Wood v. Zahradnick, No. 77-1627
      - Daniels v. Railroad Retirement Bd., No. 77-1639
      - United States v. Montgomery, No. 77-1651
      - Johnson v. Hampton, No. 77-1656 (Box 50)
      - United States v. Mogavero, No. 77-1659
      - United States v. Woolfolk, No. 77-1690
      - Virginia Materials Corp. v. Commissioner, No. 77-1710
      - United States v. Pomponio, No. 77-1719
      - Jefferson v. First and Merchants Nat'l Bank, No. 77-1724
      - United States v. Patton, No. 77-1732
      - Thomas v. Shields, No. 77-1787
      - United States v. Squires, No. 77-1802
      - United States v. Stacy, No. 77-1827
      - United States v. Cobbs, No. 77-1854
      - United States v. Bunkis, No. 77-1873
      - United States v. Robinson, No. 77-1874
      - Henry v. Textron, Inc., No. 77-1888
      - Scheel v. Conboy, No. 77-1900
      - Cantrell v. Califano, No. 77-1918
      - Potomac Elec. Power Co. v. Allied Aviation Fueling Co., No. 77-1933
      - United States v. Griffin, No. 77-1953
      - United States v. Watson, No. 77-1974
      - Brake v. Adams, No. 77-1988
      - United States v. Ranger Constr. Co., No. 77-1991
      - Westvaco Corp. v. Mappus, No. 77-2021
      - United States v. Pollock, No. 77-2041
      - District of Columbia Fed'n of Civic Ass'ns v. Adams, No. 77-2060
      - Cobb v. United States, No. 77-2063 (Box 51)